(Howard:)Except for AppleCare.
(Howard:)That pays for itself
in the long run.
(Raj:)Hi.
(Leonard:)Hey, where'd you go?
(Penny:)I got you a little something
to cheer you up.
(Leonard:)Really?
(Leonard:)Sex last night,
pancakes this morning--
(Leonard:)Am I dying?
(chuckles)
(Penny:)Just open it.
(Leonard:)A cap and gown?
(Leonard:)Why do I need a cap and gown?
(Penny:)Because you are giving
your commencement speech.
(Leonard:)What are you talking about?
(Penny:)I called your old high school
(Penny:)and convinced them to let you
give your speech over Skype.
(Leonard:)Really?
That's amazing!
(Leonard:)And you gave me the robes
to give it in.
(Leonard:)Thank you.
(Penny:)Yeah, now about those--
(Penny:)uh, they came from
a costume shop,
(Penny:)and all they had left
was sexy graduate,
(Penny:)so they...
(Penny:)might be a little short.
(Leonard:)Short and sexy,
that's my wheelhouse.
Yeah!